http://www.dollsofindia.com/privacy/

Please wait...
Sign in
Shopping Cart (0)
Favorites (0)
Home
Privacy Policy
DollsOfIndia is committed to respecting and protecting your personal privacy. Our Privacy Policy and your control over the information you provide us is outlined below.
INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM YOU OR YOUR COMPUTER
You can visit our site and use many of our services without having to tell us who you are or reveal any personally identifiable information to us. It is only when you buy items from our site,
make specific queries from us or leave reviews for items or articles on our website, through our website or through direct emails to any e-mail address, ending with @dollsofindia.com, that you will be asked to provide us with personally identifiable information.
Whenever you visit DollsOfIndia, our web server logs automatically receive and record anonymous information from your web browser including your IP Address, Referring page, the DollsOfIndia page(s) you request, and any search terms you query in our site.
DollsOfIndia uses this anonymous information to customize your experience on our site, maintain computer-specific shopping carts and to improve our services. We ordinarily do not attempt to link this information to a specific person, with certain important exceptions.
By providing us with personally identifiable information, you agree to receive communication from our end, which may or may not be limited to the resolution of a query posed by you. Please take a look at the INFORMATION REMOVAL OR UPDATION section below for asking us to remove you from our mailing/services database.
DollsOfIndia uses personally identifiable information for three main purposes: to fulfill your orders for our products, to tell you about special offers and new products and services, and to send you articles of cultural interest. Regular sending of emails, (in the form of newsletters) will be limited to users who have signed up as members or have placed an order with us.
INFORMATION REMOVAL OR UPDATION
Users, whose email/contact information are with us, may choose not to receive any future mailings/services from us by visiting this link or by writing to please enable javascript to view. You may also contact us at our address or phone number provided below. By writing in to us you can:
Request us to remove any personally identifiable information with us. This also implies that there cannot be any form of checking from our side to any future subscriptions to our services/mailings to contact addresses (physical or email) which points to you.
Request us to block any future mailings to your contact addresses (physical or email).
Users, whose email/contact information are with us, may choose to update their contact information with us by writing to please enable javascript to view. You may also contact us at our address or phone number provided below.
PRIVACY OF INFORMATION
DollsOfIndia will not share personally identifiable information with other companies or individuals unless:
We have your express permission to share the information
We need to share your information with any of our partner companies/individuals in order to provide a product or service that you have requested. Unless we tell you otherwise, these partners do not have the right to use your personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary to deliver your requested product or service.
We comply with subpoenas or court orders
Except as we've just explained above, DollsOfIndia will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information to anyone.
INFORMATION SECURITY
DollsOfIndia has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
DollsOfIndia and its partner electronic payment gateway collects all financial information required for Billing in a 256 bit SSL Secure Environment.
PRIVACY POLICY MODIFICATIONS
DollsOfIndia may modify its privacy policy from time to time. The responsibility of updating your knowledge about the same rests with you and the same can be done by visiting this page at regular intervals.
DOLLSOFINDIA CONTACT INFORMATION REGARDING CONCERNS
To request for unsubscription OR removal from our customer database OR modification or of customer information OR
clarifications on our privacy policy: please enable javascript to view
You may write to our physical address with any of the requests above. Write to:
Madhuri Guin
DollsofIndia Ecommerce Private Limited
P3B-085, Princeton Estate
DLF City Phase V
Gurgaon
Haryana 122 009
INDIA
You may contact us on our phone number : +91-7678471670.
Testimonials
I am fond of the products found in Dolls of India. Please keep the good work up.					- Rini Mitra
I ordered both sets of the gold plated white bangles.
They arrrived today and are so beautiful I...					- Nadia
Loove your website everything is beautiful.					- Kalika Monroe
I visited your website and I think you site has some really good stuff.					- Susan Phillips
I loved the necklaces!					- Archonto Souvalioti-Diggle
Read more »
Aggregated content:
Thermocol Crafts|Miniature Paintings|Sponge Wood Arts|Parvati Posters|Terracotta Sculpture|Garment|Paper Dolls|Vishvarupa|Dancing Ganesha Paintings|Hindu Statues
Privacy
Terms
Shipping
Returns
About Us
Links
Dolls of India, P3B-085, Princeton Estate, DLF Phase 5, Gurgaon 122 009, Haryana, INDIA, Tel: +917678471670
Already a member?
BUY MORE TO SAVE MORE
ADDITIONAL 10% OFF
WHEN YOU BUY FOUR OR MORE ITEMS TOGETHER
